[
  {
    "question": "An address system that keeps track of web documents and specifies where a resource can be found on the internet",
    "answer": "URL",
    "choices": [
      "HTTP",
      "HTML",
      "Hyperlink"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A network transfer protocol to find documents between a server and the browser",
    "answer": "HTTP",
    "choices": [
      "URL",
      "HTML",
      "DNS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A text string tied to an URL, used to jump from one document to another.",
    "answer": "Hyperlinks",
    "choices": [
      "HTTP",
      "DNS",
      "URL"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It provies a human-readable address to access a website on the internet",
    "answer": "Domain Name",
    "choices": [
      "HTML",
      "Hyperlinks",
      "Testing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Unique address or identifier that belongs to a device linked to a network, it's made of a series of numbers separated by dots",
    "answer": "IP",
    "choices": [
      "Hyperlinks",
      "HTTP",
      "DNS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A computer that stores a website's component files, it's connected to the internect and supports data interchange with other devices connected to the web",
    "answer": "Web server",
    "choices": [
      "Web site",
      "Hyperlinks",
      "Domain name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A global system that takes a human-readable name and translates it into it's IP",
    "answer": "DNS",
    "choices": [
      "Web site",
      "Hyperlinks",
      "Domain name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A worldwide network of connections between machines",
    "answer": "Internet",
    "choices": [
      "DNS",
      "Hyperlinks",
      "WWW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Interconnected system of public webpages that uses the HTTP protocol",
    "answer": "WWW",
    "choices": [
      "Web site",
      "HTML",
      "IP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Descriptive language that specifies a webpage structure and semantics",
    "answer": "HTML",
    "choices": [
      "CSS",
      "DNS",
      "WWW"
    ]
  }
]